http://www.swapalease.com/help/privacy.aspx

SWAPALEASE INC. PRIVACY STATEMENT LAST UPDATED: 12/1/2013
This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for www.swapalease.com of Swapalease Inc.'s Website and encompasses the following items:
What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site
The organization collecting the information
How the information is used
With whom the information may be shared
What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information
The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Swapalease Inc. control
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
If you have questions pertaining to the Swapalease Inc. privacy policy or feel that they are not abiding by what is posted, you should contact Swapalease Inc. by calling (866) 792-7669 or emailing privacy@swapalease.com.
Information Collection and Use
Swapalease Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We may sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Swapalease Inc. collects information from our users at several different points on our website.
Registration
General Perspective:
It is not necessary for a user to register in order to browse the Swapalease Inc. Web Site; however, it is recommended so that the staff at Swapalease Inc. can keep users posted of new inventory, site promotions, and special events. It will also allow personalization of the web site when the user returns in the future.
Lease "Seller's" Perspective:
In order to advertise or list a vehicle on this website, a user must first complete the required listing sections. During registration a user is required to provide sensitive information (such as credit card number including expiration date), in addition to contact information (such as name and email address), and demographic information (such as zip code). This information is principally used for listing advertisement purposes and the collection of any listing fee due Swapalease Inc.
Secondarily, Swapalease Inc. as well as potential buyers will utilize contact information for correspondence purposes.
Lease "Buyer's" Perspective:
In order to register as buyer, a user must first complete the required buyer registration sections. During registration a user is required to provide sensitive information (such as credit card number including expiration date), in addition to contact information (such as name and email address), and demographic information (such as zip code). This information is principally used for the collection of any buyer registration fee due Swapalease Inc. Secondarily, Swapalease Inc. as well as potential sellers will utilize contact information for correspondence purposes.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Swapalease uses cookies to enhance the users experience on the site and to track user behavior while visiting the site.
If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site.
The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.
Web Beacons
We employ [or our third party advertising partner employs] a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We do collect log files pertaining to domain names, access times, pages visited, and browser type. These files are not linked to personally identifiable information and are only used for the sole purpose of site management.
Sharing
We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.
We use an outside credit card processing company to bill users for services. This company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Swapalease Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
Surveys & Contests
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. If these surveys or contests are administered by a 3rd party, the information you provide will be given to the 3rd party and the 3rd party’s privacy policy will apply.
Security
This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.
When our registration form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, your browser will indicate the secure status. To learn more about SSL, follow this link www.verisign.com.
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage.
If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to security@swapalease.com.
Supplementation of Information
In order for this website to properly fulfill its obligation to our customers, it may be necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources.
For example, to determine if our customers qualify (meet generally accepted leasing company credit standards) for lease transfers it may be necessary for us to use their name and social security number to request a credit report. Once we determine a user's creditworthiness, this document is handled in a matter consistent with Fair Credit Reporting Act guidelines.
Special Offers
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, and special deals. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications.
Site and Service Updates
We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone.
Correction/Updating Personal Information
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. One way this can be accomplished is at the "Managing Your Account" page after member log in. Other avenues include emailing, phoning, or standard mailing our customer support site (see "Contact Us" page for detailed information).
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
Choice/Opt-out
Our users are notified of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. Users who no longer wish to receive memorandums or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by contacting that partner directly.
Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not.
Tell-A-Friend
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Swapalease Inc. stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.
Your friend may contact us at support@swapalease.com to request that we remove this information from our database.
Swapalease Inc. Blog
If you use the Swapalease Inc. Blog on this Web site, you should be aware than any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will notate the date of the last update at the top of this page.
Users will be responsible for understanding any changes made including changes relating to how we use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected.
Legal Disclaimer
Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.
Contact Information
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:
